onagofly.com 2016-05-27

# Privacy - ONAGOfly

This Privacy Policy describes the policies and procedures of Onago Inc. (“we”, “our” or “us”) on the collection, use and disclosure of your information on www.onagofly.com and the services, features, content, applications, and products we offer (collectively, the “Application”). When you use the Services, you are consenting to the collection, transfer, manipulation, storage, disclosure and other uses of your information as described in this Privacy Policy.

TYPES OF DATA COLLECTED

This Privacy Policy covers the treatment of personally identifiable information (“Personal Data”) gathered when you are using or accessing the Application. Among the types of Personal Data that this Application collects, by itself or through third parties, there are: Cookies, Usage Data and Email.

Other Personal Data collected may be described in other sections of this Privacy Policy or by dedicated explanation text contextually with the Personal Data collection.

•   The Personal Data may be freely provided by the User, or collected automatically when using this Application.  
•   Any use of Cookies - or of other tracking tools - by this Application or by the owners of third party services used by this Application, unless stated otherwise, serves to identify Users and remember their preferences, for the sole purpose of providing the service required by the User.  
•   Failure to provide certain Personal Data may make it impossible for this Application to provide its services.  
•   The User assumes responsibility for the Personal Data of third parties published or shared through this Application and declares to have the right to communicate or broadcast them, thus relieving the Data Controller of all responsibility.

METHODS AND PLACE OF PROCESSING

The Data Controller processes the Personal Data of Users in a proper manner and shall take appropriate security measures to prevent unauthorized access, disclosure, modification, or unauthorized destruction of the Personal Data.

The data processing is carried out using computers and/or IT enabled tools, following organizational procedures and modes strictly related to the purposes indicated.

GOOGLE ANALYTICS (GOOGLE)

Google Analytics is a web analysis service provided by Google Inc. (“Google”). Google utilizes the Personal Data collected to track and examine the use of this Application, to prepare reports on its activities and share them with other Google services.

•   Google may use the Personal Data collected to contextualize and personalize the ads of its own advertising network.  
•   Personal Data collected: Cookie and Usage Data.  
•   Place of processing : USA – [Privacy Policy](http://www.google.com/intl/en/policies/privacy/) – [Opt Out](https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout?hl=en)

DISPLAYING CONTENT FROM EXTERNAL PLATFORMS

These services allow you to view content hosted on external platforms directly from the pages of this Application and interact with them. If a service of this kind is installed, it may still collect web traffic data for the pages where the service is installed, even when users do not use it.

YouTube.com

•   YouTube is a video content visualization service provided by YouTube that allows this Application to incorporate content of this kind on its pages.  
•   Personal Data collected: Cookie and Usage Data.  
•   Place of processing : USA – [Privacy Policy](http://www.youtube.com/yt/policyandsafety/policy.html)

INTERACTION WITH EXTERNAL SOCIAL NETWORKS AND PLATFORMS

These services allow interaction with social networks or other external platforms directly from the pages of this Application.

•   The interaction and information obtained by this Application are always subject to the User’s privacy settings for each social network.  
•   If a service enabling interaction with social networks is installed it may still collect traffic data for the pages where the service is installed, even when Users do not use it.

Twitter Tweet Button and Social Widgets (Twitter)

•   The Twitter Tweet button and social widgets are services allowing interaction with the Twitter social network provided by Twitter Inc.  
•   Personal Data collected: Cookie and Usage Data.  
•   Place of processing : USA – [Privacy Policy](https://twitter.com/privacy?lang=en)

Facebook Like Button and Social Widgets (Facebook)

•   The Facebook Like button and social widgets are services allowing interaction with the Facebook social network provided by Facebook, Inc.  
•   Personal Data collected: Cookie and Usage Data.  
•   Place of processing : USA – [Privacy Policy](https://www.facebook.com/privacy/explanation)

ADVERTISING

To help us deliver ads (remarketing), measure their performance, and make them more relevant to you based on criteria like your activity in our application we use cookies and pixels to tailor ads and measure their performance. Using these technologies, we can show you ads and evaluate their effectiveness. This helps us provide high-quality ads and content that might be more interesting to you.

•   If you would like to change the way we collect data about you in Twitter, visit [Twitter account settings](https://twitter.com/settings/security), [Do Not Track browser setting](https://support.twitter.com/articles/20169453), and the [opt-out choices of Twitter's ads](https://support.twitter.com/articles/20170407#our-ad-partners).  
•   Our third-party advertising providers, including Google Analytics for Display Advertisers, also use these technologies for marketing on our behalf, including the delivery of interest-based ads and measurement of their performance.  
•   If you do not want our advertising providers to use your visits to Twitter websites to show you personalized ads on our behalf, you can opt out using your [Do Not Track browser setting](https://support.twitter.com/articles/20169453).  
•   You can also opt out of Google Analytics by installing Google’s [opt-out browser add-on](https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout), and out of interest-based Google ads using [Google’s Ads Settings](https://www.google.com/settings/u/0/ads/authenticated). To opt out of activity-based ads in Facebook, visit your [Facebook Ad Settings](https://www.facebook.com/settings?tab=ads).

MANAGING EMAIL ADDRESSES AND SENDING MESSAGES

These services make it possible to manage a database of subscription based email contacts to communicate with the User via email. The services are used to collect data concerning the date and time when the mail is viewed by the User, as well as when the User interacts with incoming mail, such as by clicking on links included in the email.

MailChimp

•   MailChimp is an email address management and message sending service provided by The Rocket Science Group, LLC d/b/a MailChimp, a State of Georgia limited liability company. Personal Data collected: Email address.  
•   Place of processing : United States – [Privacy Policy](http://mailchimp.com/legal/privacy/)

ADDITIONAL INFORMATION ABOUT DATA COLLECTION

LEGAL ACTION

The User's Personal Data may be used for legal purposes by the Data Controller, in Court or in the stages leading to possible legal action arising from improper use of this Application or the related services. The User is aware of the fact that the Data Controller may be required to reveal Personal Data upon request of public authorities.

ADDITIONAL INFORMATION ABOUT USERS' PERSONAL DATA

In addition to the information contained in this Privacy Policy, this Application may provide the User with additional and contextual information concerning particular services or the collection and processing of Personal Data upon request.

SYSTEM LOGS AND MAINTENANCE

For operation and maintenance purposes, this Application and any third party services may collect files that record interaction with this Application (System Logs) or use for this purpose other Personal Data (such as IP Address).

INFORMATION NOT CONTAINED IN THIS PRIVACY POLICY

More details concerning the collection or processing of Personal Data may be requested from the Data Controller at any time. Please see the contact information at the end of this Privacy Policy.

THE RIGHTS OF USERS

Users have the right, at any time, to know whether their Personal Data has been stored and can consult the Data Controller to learn about their contents and origin, to verify their accuracy or to ask for them to be supplemented, cancelled, updated or corrected, or for their transformation into anonymous format or to block any data held in violation of the law, as well as to oppose their treatment for any and all legitimate reasons. Requests should be sent to the Data Controller at the contact information set out below. This Application does not support “Do Not Track” requests. To determine whether any of the third party services it uses honor the “Do Not Track” requests, please read their privacy policies.

CHANGES TO THIS PRIVACY POLICY

The Data Controller reserves the right to make changes to this Privacy Policy at any time by giving notice to its Users on this page. It is strongly recommended to check this page often, referring to the date of the last modification listed at the bottom. If a User objects to any of the changes to this Privacy Policy, the User must cease using this Application and can request that the Data Controller erase the Personal Data. Unless stated otherwise, the then-current privacy policy applies to all Personal Data the Data Controller has about Users.

INFORMATION ABOUT THIS PRIVACY POLICY

The Data Controller is responsible for this Privacy Policy.

DATA CONTROLLER AND OWNER

ONAGO Inc.  
hello@onagofly.com

Congratulations! You've reached the end. Thanks for taking the time to read this Privacy Policy.

Copyright © 2016 ONAGO Inc. All rights reserved.

Updated by ONAGO Inc. on November 15, 2015
